U.S. Emergency Board No. 154 Records 5062
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
U.S. Emergency Board No. 154 Records
1962-1969
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
U.S. Emergency Board
5062
1 cubic feet
1 linear ft.
Records (documents), sources.
Transcript of proceedings and exhibits of the Emergency Board No. 154. Eastern, Western, and Southeastern Carriers Conference Committee and the Brotherhood of Locomotive Engineers, the Brotherhood of Locomotive Firemen and Enginemen, the Order of Railway Conductors and Brakemen, the Brotherhood of Railroad Trainment and the Switchmen's Union of North America.
3115650
General
Contact Information:
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation and Archives Martin P. Catherwood Library 227 Ives Hall Cornell University Ithaca, NY 14853 (607) 255-3183 kheel_center@cornell.edu http://www.ilr.cornell.edu/library/kheel-center
Compiled by:
Kheel Staff, September 25, 2014
EAD encoding:
Kheel Staff, March 07, 2019
Conditions Governing Access
Access to the collections in the Kheel Center is restricted. Please contact a reference archivist for access to these materials.
Related Materials
Related Collections: railroad union collections
Arbitration, Industrial -- United States -- Sources; Railroads -- Employees -- Labor unions -- United States -- Sources; Brotherhood of Locomotive Engineers (U.S.) -- Sources; Brotherhood of Locomotive Firemen and Enginemen -- Sources; Brotherhood of Railroad Trainmen -- Sources; Order of Railway Conductors and Brakemen -- Sources; Switchmen's Union of North America -- Sources
3115650
- Transcripts Vol. 1 (Box 1, Folder 1)
- Transcripts Vol. 1 Copy 2 (Box 1, Folder 2)
- Carrier's Exhibition No. 1, 1963 (Box 1, Folder 3)
- Carrier's Exhibition No. 2, 1963 (Box 1, Folder 4)
- Carrier's Exhibition No. 3, 1963 (Box 1, Folder 5)
- Carrier's Exhibition No. 4, 1963 (Box 1, Folder 6)
- Carrier's Exhibition No. 5, 1963 (Box 1, Folder 7)
- Carrier's Exhibition No. 6, 1963 (Box 1, Folder 8)
- Carrier's Exhibition No. 7, 1963 (Box 1, Folder 9)
- Carrier's Exhibition No. 8, 1963 (Box 1, Folder 10)
- Carrier's Exhibition No. 9, 1963 (Box 1, Folder 11)
- Carrier's Exhibition No. 10, 1963 (Box 1, Folder 12)
- Carrier's Exhibition No. 11, 1963 (Box 1, Folder 13)
- Carrier's Exhibition No. 12, 1963 (Box 1, Folder 14)
- Carrier's Exhibition No. 13, 1963 (Box 1, Folder 15)
- Carrier's Exhibition No. 15, 1963 (Box 1, Folder 16)
- Employees Exhibit No. 1, 1963 (Box 1, Folder 17)
- Employees Exhibit No. 4 (Box 1, Folder 18)
- Employees Exhibit No. 11 (Box 1, Folder 19)
- Employees Exhibit No. 18 (Box 1, Folder 20)
- Employees Exhibit no. 109 (Box 1, Folder 21)
- Employees Exhibits un-numbered (Box 1, Folder 22)
- Employees Exhibit No. 1 and 2 (Box 1, Folder 23)
- Exhibits (Box 1, Folder 24)
- Switching (Box 1, Folder 25)
- Statement of Position of the Switching Union (Box 1, Folder 26)
- Glossary (Box 1, Folder 27)
- Correspondence (Box 1, Folder 28)
- Manpower Development and Training Act, 1969 (Box 1, Folder 29)
- Rail Maker Legislation, 1962 (Box 1, Folder 30)
- Report to the President, 1963 (Box 1, Folder 31)